Guide to the Missionary Ephemera Collection
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Posters, Illustrations, Banners, Series IX
  - China
    - Set of posters with flannel on the back and corresponding notes depicting "Pilgrim's Progress", no date (Box OV9, Folder 7)
    - 1 blue embroidered banner with tassels, no date (Box OV9, Folder 8)
    - 2 red scrolls, no date (Box OV9, Folder 9)
    - 1-10 of 40 black-rimmed posters published by the Religious Tract Society of Hankow and Shanghai., 1930s (Box OVd15-#1)
      1) "Thou shalt have no other gods before me." Cat. No. 3092 (for 1934) 2) "Victory through the cross" Cat. No. 3074 3) "Beware" Cat. No. 19088 (for 1933) 4) "Death to life" Cat. No. 19305 (for 1935) 5) "Satan's snare" (for 1933) 6) "Between two opinions" Cat. No. 3094 (for 1934) 7) "The lamb of God" Cat. No. 19322 (for 1938) 8) "Thou shalt have no other gods before me" Cat. No. 3092 (for 1934) 9) "Gone astray" Cat. No. 3093 (for 1934) 10) "Ladder to heaven" Cat. No. 19321 (for 1938)
    - 11-20 of 40 black-rimmed posters published by the Religious Tract Society of Hankow and Shanghai., 1930s (Box OVd15-#2)
      11) "The life saver" Cat. No. 19311 (for 1936) 12) "Entering into salvation" Cat. No. 19316 (1937) 13) "Sin as 'Barrier'" Cat. No. 19307 (for 1936) 14) "Invitation to knock" Cat. No. 19315 (1937) 15) "The wrong entrance" Cat. No. 19314 (1937) 16) "The door closed" Cat. No. 19318 (1937) 17) "Victory through the cross" Cat. No. 3074 18) "Grace" Cat. No. 18306 (for 1935) 19) "Urging others to enter" Cat. No. 19317 (1937) 20) "What shall it profit a man?" Cat. No. 3095 (for 1934)
    - 21-30 of 40 black-rimmed posters published by the Religious Tract Society of Hankow and Shanghai., 1930s (Box OVd15-#3)
      21) "The path of safety" Cat. No. 19087 22) "Doubt" Cat. No. 3304 (for 1935) 23) "Forgiveness" Cat. No. 3303 (for 1935) 24) "Danger" Cat. No. 18302 (for 1935) 25) "Be not deceived" Cat. No. 3096 (for 1934) 26) "Good fruit" Cat. No. 19320 (for 1938) 27) "Take heed" (for 1933) 28) "The new man" Cat. No. 19312 (for 1936) 29) damaged poster – no title remaining 30) "Life and death" Cat. No. 19301 (for 1935)
    - 31-40 of 40 black-rimmed posters published by the Religious Tract Society of Hankow and Shanghai., 1930s (Box OVd15-#4)
      31) "Decision time" Cat. No. 19324 (for 1938) 32) "The cross as gate" Cat. No. 19310 (for 1936) 33) "The axe and tree" Cat. No. 19319 (for 1938) 34) "The substitute" Cat. No. 3308 (for 1936) 35) "The horrible pit" 36) "Ladder to heaven" Cat. No. 19321 (for 1938) 37) "True freedom" 38) "The life saver" Cat. No. 19311 (for 1936) 39) "The horrible pit" Cat. No. 3075 40) "Beware" Cat. NO. 19088 (for 1933)
    - 14 posters of various kinds all published by the Religious Tract Society of Hankow and Shanghai., no date (Box OVd15-#5)
      1/2) 2 of the same poster – "Turn Ye! Turn Ye!" Cat. No. 19073 3) Pictorial Preaching Series Miss C. F. Tippet "The two roads" Cat. No. 3250 4) "The Nativity" (after copping) Cat. No. 19325 (1940) 5) "The good shepherd" Cat. No. 19334 (1941) 6) "Messiah is the lamb of God" Cat. No. 3097 (for 1934) 7) "Joy and rejoicing" 8) "Word as a mirror" Cat. No. 3072 9) Pictorial Preaching Series Miss C. F. Tippet "Journeying heavenward" Cat. No. 3251 B 10) "The Parable of the Sower" Cat. No. 3086 11) "From death unto life" 12) "Turn Ye! Turn Ye!" 13) "Welcome" (for 1933) 14) "Fans of the four seasons" Cat. No. 3087
    - 2 long posters with Chinese characters and no pictures, no date (Box OVd15-#6)
    - 1 poster published by The Phonetic Promotion Committee, entitled "Jesus the Saviour", no date (Box OVd15-#7)
    - 1 poster with the notation "Committee-27-G", no date (Box OVd15-#8)
    - 4 posters without indication of publisher or title. The final poster has a note that says it is about St. Luke's Gospel., no date (Box OVd15-#9)
    - 3 colored Chinese posters, no date (Box OVd1-#16, Folder 1)
      One poster has ten household scenes on it. One poster shows a family learning and worshipping. One poster has some Latin at the bottom that reads, "Sexcentesimo Exeunte Anno Ab Obitu Piissimo Beati Odorici A Portunaone O.F.M. Qui Inter Primos Missionales Evangelium Sinensibus Nuntiavit Utini, Die 14 Januarii 1331-1931."
    - 8 assorted Chinese missionary posters without any English indication of publisher., no date (Box OVd1-#16, Folder 2)
    - 2 Chinese posters with Bible verses on them., no date (Box OVd1-#16, Folder 3)
      They are white posters with black Chinese characters on them. One says "What shall it profit a man – and lose his soul." The other is John 5:28-29.
    - 4 Chinese posters published by the China Baptist Publication Society, Canton, China., no date (Box OVd1-#16, Folder 4)
      The poster labeled No. 2 is titled "Gambling Evil", the one labeled No. 3 is titled "Drinking Evil", the one labeled No. 6 is titled "The Social Evil", and the one labeled No. 7 is titled "The Drug Evil".
    - 1 rectangular Chinese poster in red, white, and blue, with Chinese symbols and an airplane on it., no date (Box OVd1-#17, Folder 1)
    - 10 rectangular Chinese posters labeled "V.E. Scrolls 'Sin, Salvation, Purity, Glory.' Cat. 3088., no date (Box OVd1-#17, Folder 2)
      These posters are published by the Religious Tract Society, Hankow & Shanghai." The posters are either black, red, or yellow. The black and red posters have white symbols, while the yellow posters have red symbols.
    - 36 rectangular Chinese posters on semi-transparent paper. The posters are either off-white, pink, peach, blue, or teal. The Chinese characters and few drawings are all in black ink., no date (Box OVd1-#17, Folder 3)
    - Colored poster published by the Religious Tract Society for China, Hankow and Shanghai. There are 9 panels on the poster with different scenes of home life., no date (Box OVd1-#18, Folder 1)
    - 9 assorted Chinese posters in color, no date (Box OVd1-#18, Folder 2)
    - 7 white, red, and black Chinese posters, no date (Box OVd1-#18, Folder 3)
    - 9 posters published by the Christian Book Room, Shanghai., no date (Box OVd1-#18, Folder 4)
    - 5 Chinese posters published by the Religious Tract Society, Hankow & Shanghai., no date (Box OVd4-#19, Folder 1)
      All of the posters are V.E. Half Size Posters. One is labeled "A New Objective", another "The Lotus", another "A New Outlook", and the last "Sin and Death".
    - 3 Chinese posters in a similar artistic style published by the Religious Tract Society, Hankow & Shanghai., no date (Box OVd4-#19, Folder 2)
      One is labeled "V.E. Half Size Poster 'Rich Fool' Cat. No. 3085". The second is labeled "V.E. Half Size Poster 'An Old Invitation Renewed' Cat. No. 3078". The third is labeled "V.E. Half Size Poster 'A New Friend' Cat. No. 3081".
    - 2 Chinese posters published by the Religious Tract Society for China, Hankow and Shanghai. They are both labeled, "Cat No. 1012 'Family at prayer'". Each has five images on it and many Chinese characters., no date (Box OVd4-#19, Folder 3)
    - 3 Chinese posters published by the Religious Tract Society for China, Hankow and Shanghai. Each has nine panels with images of home life on them. Two are also labeled "CAT. No. 1011 'Man At Work'"., no date (Box OVd4-#20, Folder 1)
    - 3 white, black, and green Chinese posters published by the Religious Tract Society, Hankow & Shanghai. Two of the posters are labeled "V.E. Half Size Poster 'A new Chance' Cat. No. 3082.", no date (Box OVd4-#20, Folder 2)
    - 4 colored posters with similar layouts and symbols (images of the sea and houses). (Box OVd4-#20, Folder 3)
      One of them explicitly states that it was published by the Christian Book Room, which probably means that they all were.
    - 3 posters published by the Missionary Bulletin., no date (Box OVd4-#20, Folder 4)
      They are in color and on slightly more sturdy paper than most of the posters.
    - 4 Chinese rectangular posters published by the Religious Tract Society, Hankow. They are entitled "V.E. Scroll 'Peace and Trouble' Cat. No. 20105." The posters are all white, black, and green., no date (Box OVd15-#21, Folder 1)
  - Dutch
    - Small poster of Monseigneur Theotimus Verhaeghen, no date (Box OV8, Folder 1)
    - Small poster regarding Norse Missions, 1940 (Box OV8, Folder 2)
  - Egypt/Middle East
    - Two missionary cards (SPCK) used for education in the Middle East, no date (Box OV8, Folder 3)
      One represents the Nunc Dimittis and the other the return of the Prodigal Son.
    - Collection of 32 posters on Egypt by The Comite Catholique Contre la Faim et pour le Developpement, or CCFD, 1981 (Box OV8, Folder 4)
      The CCFD was founded in France in 1961 by the Catholic Church in order to mobilize Christians in the fight against hunger. The collection is complete in every respect, including the explanatory index sheets.
  - India
    - Poster entitled, "Apostle of Peace & Unity," printed by Dayals' Press Delhi and published by Paul Picture Publishers., no date (Box OVd1-#13, Folder 4)
  - Papua New Guinea
    - Numerous posters and teaching aids published by Liturgical Catechetical Institute, Goroka (Box OV11)
  - Sweden
    - Swedish poster of "Scandinavian Missionary Flights: Member of The World Missionary Aviation Conference". The poster has a cross and a plane on it., no date (Box OVd15-#15)
  - English language
    - 15 Mission Pictures for 4's and 5's, Set 1, no date (Box OV8, Folder 5)
      This is not a complete set of the series. It includes Japan, New Mexico, Chile, Brazil, Mexico, and the Philippines. Published by the Woman's Missionary Union.
    - Poster entitled, "A Missionary Doctor Helps People," printed by United Church Press in the USA, 1963 (Box OV8, Folder 6)
    - 4 English-language posters, no date (Box OVd1-#10)
      1) Poster entitled, "Into All the World: Your New Missionaries 1951". Published by the Board of World Missions, Presbyterian Church U.S., Nashville, TN. Includes faces of missionaries on top of a world map. 2-4) Three posters entitled, "And now in 1,000 Tongues" published by the American Bible Society, Bible House, New York City.
  - French language
    - French Missionary Poster with the handwritten caption, "Souvenir de l'Ecole Saint-Jean de Ckol-Avolo (Essé) a Monsieur l'Administrateur adjoint des Polonies J.J. Delabrousse lors de son depart en conge.", March 28, 1957 (Box OV8, Folder 7)
    - Colored wood block print of the massacre of missionaries in China. Beneath the image is a short article in French about the event., 19th century (Box OV8, Folder 8)
    - 2 French-language posters, no date (Box OVd1-#11)
      1) French-language Belgian poster that reads, "Journée Missionnaire Universelle 18 Octobre Priez, Communiez Épargnez Pour Les Missions Faites-Vous Membre De La Propagation De La Foi." 2) Movie poster for Un missionnaire, a 1954 French film by Maurice Cloche. The plot is about a Young Father, Jean Maurel, full of illusions and enthusiasm, arriving in Guinea to the mission Affob directed for 30 years by Father Gauthier. He dreams of heroic adventures and even martyrdom, but when Father Gauthier leaves Africa, he meets only disappointments and failures. He falls ill and is repatriated, but with a strengthened faith. Repaired on back.
    - Large poster entitled "Soeurs De St. Paul De Chartres En Partance Pour Les Missions Étrangéres" with the words "Enseignantes Hospitalieres Missionnaires" on the image of missionaries and angels in a boat., no date (Box OVd1-#14, Folder 2)
  - Italian language
    - "Beato Odorico Da Pordenone: Missionario In Cina Nel Secolo XIV" poster. A monk holds a book and points toward the sky in the image on this poster., no date (Box OV8, Folder 12)
    - Poster with Christ in front of the Vatican and people from various countries at His feet. Beneath Christ the poster reads, "Omnes Gentes Servient Ei.", February 2, 1928 (Box OV8, Folder 13)
      The title of the poster is "Sua Santità esprime il voto ardente che tutti I Fedeli si ascrivano alla Pontificia Opera della Propagazione della Fede." The date is February 2, 1928 and it lists Cardinal Gasparri as the Secretary of State.
    - Poster of a missionary baptizing an African man with Mary in the clouds above them, no date (Box OV8, Folder 14)
      The poster reads, "La mano del Missionario potrà alrarsi sul capo dell'infedele, se la mano del Benefattore l'aiuterà a raggiungere il suo ideale." The back has various Missionary information on it.
    - Poster entitled, "Missione Vincenziana Ricordo Dei Missionari.", no date (Box OV8, Folder 15)
      On the poster, Mary is standing on the globe and around her the poster reads, "O Maria Concepita Senza Peccato Pregate Per Noi Che Ricorriamo A Voi."
    - 3 Italian-language posters, 1952-1954 (Box OVd1-#12)
      1) 1954 Catholic Italian Missionary Poster. It reads, "Mediante la Base Missionaria l'Azione Cattolica ha già iniziato un lavoro unitario col quale esce dalle sue sedi per andare a portare la verità ai lontani ~Pius pp. XII." There is a car labeled Base Missionaria on it full of people. 2) 1953 Italian Missionary Poster Giornata Missionaria Mondiale. The subtitle reads, "La Carità Per I Poveri Di Ogni Terra Di Ogni Fede." 3) 1952 Giornata Missionaria Mondiale Italian Missionary Poster. The poster also reads, "Il Vangelo messaggio di verità di giustizia e di pace," with the precise date of October 19, 1952. The image is of a nun reading to two Asian children in a field of flowers.
  - Spanish language
    - Small poster of Argentinian Ceferino Namuncura, no date (Box OV8, Folder 16)
      The poster has the words "Quiero Ser Util A Mi Gente" on it and a prayer printed on the back of it.
    - Spanish poster with the main title, "Apostolado De La Oracion." The poster reflects Spanish missions in Africa., March, 1959 (Box OVd1-#13, Folder 1)
    - Spanish poster with the main title, "Apostolado De La Oracion." The poster reflects Spanish missions around the world., October, 1961 (Box OVd1-#13, Folder 2)
    - Spanish poster with the main title, "Apostolado De La Oracion." The poster reflects Spanish missions around the world., September, 1958 (Box OVd1-#13, Folder 3)
- Stamps, Stationery, Series X
  - Binder full of missionary stamps from various countries, no date (Box OV5, Folder 1)
    The countries represented in this binder include: Angola, Arizona, California, Canada, China, Colombia, Ethiopia, Falkland Islands, Finland, Florida, French Polynesia, Gabon, Gambia, Gilbert and Ellice Islands, Hawaii, Honduras, India, Italy, Kenya, Lesotho, Liberia, Macau, Madagascar, Magyar, Marshall Islands, Mauritania, Michigan, Namibia, New Zealand, Norfolk Island, Norway, Oregon, Papua New Guinea, Paraguay, Portugal, Republic of Equatorial Guinea, Rhodesia, Slovenia, Solomon Islands, South Africa, Spain, Spanish Guinea, Sri Lanka (Ceylon), Suriname, Sweden, Togo, Uganda, United States of America, Vietnam, Wallis and Futuna Islands, Washington, Zambia. Most of the stamps are on envelopes associated with various Missionary groups, churches, and societies, as well as with specific people.
  - Complete set of 8 stamps of African Missions by Chocolates Batanga, 1955 (Box OV5, Folder 2)
  - Set of 8 French stamps published by Soeurs Catéchistes-Missionnaires de Marie-Immaculée, no date (Box OV5, Folder 3)
  - Two envelopes with stamps on them, postmarked from Liberia, no date (Box OV5, Folder 4)
  - Uganda and Rwanda Missionary Stamp collection containing 9 stamps, no date (Box OV5, Folder 5)
    Four stamps are from Uganda and five are from Rwanda.
  - Two sheets of vintage European Stationary with missionary themes, no date (Box OV5, Folder 6)
    One sheet of the stationary has a letter written on it.
  - First day cover of the 60th anniversary of the First Missionary Outreach Church in New Britain, 1974 (Box OV5, Folder 7)
    Double sided newsletter on history also enclosed. Envelope includes a stamp.
  - First day cover with enclosed newsletter of the 150th anniversary of the first Methodist service to the Maori people, 1973 (Box OV5, Folder 8)
    Envelope includes a stamp.
  - First day cover of the 50th anniversary of the first Mission on the North-East Coast of Bougainville in Papua, New Guinea, 1972 (Box OV5, Folder 9)
    Double sided newsletter also enclosed. Envelope includes a stamp.
  - First day cover of the 150th anniversary of the landing of the first missionary in Tonga, Walter Lawry, 1972 (Box OV5, Folder 10)
    Two-page newsletter on the history of the first Mission there is included. Envelope includes a stamp.
- Miscellaneous Items, Series XI
  - Autographs of bishops
    - Bishops of the Philippines, no date (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Bishops include: Gouverneur Frank Mosher, Lyman Cunningham Ogilby, Charles Bowen Persell Jr., George Leslie Cadigan, Raymond Adams Heron, Norman S. Binsted, Charles Henry Brent
    - Bishops of Mexico, no date (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Bishops include: Melchor Saucedo, Frank W. Creighton, Efrain Salinas y Velasco, Henry Damorel Aves
    - Bishops of South America, no date (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Bishops inlcude: David Benson Reed, Dudley Scott Stark, James Wilson Hunter, Edward Clark Turner, Allen Webster Brown, John Long Jackson
    - Bishops of Africa, no date (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Bishops include: Charles Clifton Penick, Walter Henry Overs, Conrad Herbert Gesner, Theopilius Momolu Gardiner, Vedder Van Dyck, Robert E. Campbell, John Payne, Samuel D. Ferguson, John Gottlieb Aver, Horatio Southgate
    - Bishops of China and Japan, no date (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Bishops of China: James Chang Ling Wong, Charles P. Gilson, Daniel Trumbull Huntington, Robert Franklin Wilner, Alfred A. Gilman, William J. Boone, William James Boone, John W. Nichols, Frederick Rogers Graves, Logan Herbert Roots, James Addison Ingle, Samuel Isaac Joseph Schereschensky. Bishops of Japan: Henry St. George Tucker, Charles Shriver Reifsnider, Shirley H. Nichols, Channing Moore Williams, John McKim, Sidney Catlin Partridge
    - Bishops of Connecticut, no date (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Bishops include: Samuel Seabury, Abraham Jarvis, Thomas Church Brownell, Chauncy Bunce Brewster, Edward Campion Acheson, Frederick G. Budlong, John Williams, Lloyd Rutherford Craighill, Daniel Corrigan, Richard Simpson Watson, James Loughlin Duncan
    - Miscellaneous Bishops, no date (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Bishops include: James Stuart Wetmore of New York, Henry Irving Louttit of South Florida, Richard Runkel Emery of North Dakota, Dillard Houston Brown of Liberia, James Craik Morris of Canal Zone, Summer Francis Dudley Walters of San Joaquin, John James Gravatt of Upper South Carolina, Harry Roberts Carson of Haiti, Spence Burton of Haiti and the Dominican Republic, Paul Axtell Kellogg of the Dominican Republic, Hiram Richard Hulse of Cuba, Albion Williamson Knight of Cuba, James Heartt Van Buren of Puerto Rico, Charles Blayney Colmore of Puerto Rico, Charles Francis Boynton of Puerto Rico
  - Embroidery
    - Embroidered African Lord's Prayer Missionary Tapestry and a gold-colored picture frame, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      The small gold-colored picture frame has a typewritten paper taped inside. The paper reads, "In Africa * Miss Cross' Native Girls. The Lord's Prayer Worked By One Of Miss Cross' Native Girls…………Received From Verna Hertzler While She Was A Missionary In Osaka, Japan……….Martha M. George………Given To Mrs. Gossman When Miss Cross Was Home On Furlough in 1917……."
    - Commemorative towel for the Women's Missionary Association of the Baptist Missionary Society, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Music
    - 78 r.p.m. Record used for evangelism in the South Pacific, no date (Box 15, Folder 10)
      One side has "Noah" in English on it and the other has "Christ Our Victory" in English on it.
    - Original 1898 translation of the Universal Papal Hymn into the Nez-Perce language (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Small pamphlet about St. Francis Xavier with the hymn "Lofzang", 1943 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      The hymn "Lofzang" with text by L. Monden, S.J. and music by A. Meulemans is printed on the back. It is written in Dutch.
  - Worship-related
    - Blessing Kit from the Vincentian Foreign Missionary Society, no date (Box 15, Folder 13)
      The Blessing Kit includes Holy Water (now empty) and blessed candles.
  - Yearbooks
    - 3 Yearbooks entitled, "The Scroll", Northwestern Theological Seminary and Bible Training School, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1942, 1943, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Two Yearbooks entitled, "The Book of Golden Memories", Washington Missionary College, Takoma Park, Maryland, 1933, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "The Missionarian", Nyack Missionary College, Nyack, New York, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Southern Memories", Southern Missionary College, Collegedale, Tennessee, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Photographs, Series XII
  - Africa
    - A collection of 35 photos on Missions in Uganda, 1934-1947 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      This album begins with a photo of Miss F. K. Quinlan at the C.M.S. Summer School in Malvern in August, 1934. She appears again ministering to an out-patient in Uganda. There are many pictures of the construction of the church at the Sallana Mission Station. Many also on the distribution of Bibles by the Uganda Bookshop as well as the CMS. Local industry is shown in many photos. The Chapel choir at Bishop Tucker College is shown, as well as a photo of Bupoto. Also photographed are local out-patients being treated, local industry, local church elder, and the Mission station. Photos taken over a 14 year period.
    - Collection of 15 photos on a religious procession in Leopoldville, Belgian Congo., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Collection of 6 photos of a Catholic Mission in Madagascar, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - 12 photos of Catholic Eucharist in Elizabethville, Belgian Congo, no date (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Collection of 25 photographs of the Missions Peres Blancs in the Belgian Congo, 1937-1960 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Photo collection from the Catholic mission and hospital in Mogadishu, Italian Somaliland, during the Italian occupation., no date (Box 18, Folder 6)
      The hospital shows Italians and indigenous people. 10 large format photos all with descriptions on the back.
    - Photo of an Italian military officer with a Catholic missionary in Eritrea., no date (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 3 photos from an early Italian Missione Cattolica in Eritrea, no date (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - The photo shows the procession of Corpus Christi in Mogadishu, Somalia., no date (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Photo labeled, "La processione del Corpus Domini a Mogadiscio. La testa del sacre corteo e salutata dale camicie nere."
    - Photo of boy scouts at a Catholic Mission in Egypt, Early 20th century (Box 18, Folder 10)
      A stamp on the back of the photograph reads, "Servizio Fotografico de 'L'Ambrosiano' Fotografie eseguite con Carte 'Gevaert'."
    - 10 photographs (4 of them duplicates) of a gathering in Swaziland, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      The gathering is probably a church conference or service. The people are in western dress and in one of the photographs they are singing.
    - Photo from the Belgian Congo. The sign reads, "Les Premiers Communiants remercient leurs Bienfaiteurs.", 1950 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Collection of 6 French press photos of senior religious figures in Sub-Sahara Africa., 1959-1981 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Shown are Cardinal Malula (Zaire), Abbe Fulbert Youlou (Congo), Cardinal Zoungrana (Burkina Faso), and Bernardin Gantin (Benin).
    - Collection of 7 press photos of the visit of King Baudouin to the Belgian Congo in 1955. (Box 18, Folder 14)